But isn't part of that because we had to fold everything into critical race theory and somehow the Middle East became part of, you know.
I see it differently.
And I love this conversation because I think people, those of us who went to college, give a lot more credit to college courses for how the world works than I do.
This is not about critical race theory on college campuses.
This is about Iran.
Iran and Qatar have come up with a disinformation campaign that they are running through TikTok and Instagram that is massive.
If you are a young person, you open up your phone and all you see is dead Gaza baby, dead Gaza baby, dead Gaza baby.
Diddy, dead Gaza baby, dead Gaza baby.
Why is this man following me?
Why are you following me?
Unfollow me.
I'm blocking you.
I don't want none of this kunified, zidiotic energy, even Wi-Fi-ably next to me.
Never underestimate what money can do to people.
He used to be an organizer.
Yep.
And now look at him.
Dead Gaza baby, where do you mean?
You damn rude, eh?
Yeah.